<language>
  <play>PLAY</play>
	<settings>SETTINGS</settings>
  <exit>EXIT</exit>
  <retry>RETRY</retry>
  <language>Language</language>
	<music>Music</music>
	<sound>Sound</sound>
  <accept>Accept</accept>
  <resume>Resume</resume>
  <wakeup>Wake Up</wakeup>
  <next>Next</next>
  <talk>Talk</talk>
  <grab>Grab</grab>
  <intromessage0>Hey! Are you ok? Looks like you had a boat accident. Can you hear me? Are you awake? Can you stand up?</intromessage0>
  <intromessage1>Finally, I thought you didn't make it. My name is Eyra, nice to meet you.</intromessage1>
  <intromessage2>What? Where are we? This Kattegat island, before it was a prosperous island but now...</intromessage2>
  <intromessage3>Since the dark lord took our lands, no island is monster free.</intromessage3>
  <intromessage4>Kattegat could hold until a couple of days ago, but at the end it also falls and all the inhabitants left.</intromessage4>
  <intromessage5>I am a boat builder, when I was going to my workshop to get my tools, I got trapped and everyone left leaving me here.</intromessage5>
  <intromessage6>Do you think you could help me? If you could get my tools and a bit of wood I would be able to build a boat, and we could leave together.</intromessage6>
  <intromessage7>Take this sword and bow and use it to fight against the monsters of the island. I only need my tools and 10 logs of wood.</intromessage7>
  <intromessage8>Let me heal your wounds. Good luck, if you need anything come talk to me anytime.</intromessage8>
  <whatcanido>What can I do for you?</whatcanido>
  <rest>Rest</rest>
  <logs>Wood Logs</logs>
  <tools>Tools</tools>
  <yes>Yes</yes>
  <no>No</no>
  <letsgo>Let's go</letsgo>
  <noanswer>Oh, I see, no problem. Do you need anything else?</noanswer>
  <restanswer>Do you want to rest? Rest will heal all your wounds but all the enemies will respawn, are you sure you want to rest?</restanswer>
  <restansweryes>Al right. See you tomorrow, have a nice rest!</restansweryes>
  <logsanswer>You got all the logs? I only need 10 wood logs to be able to build a boat and leave.</logsanswer>
  <logsansweryes>Perfect, thanks, with this I have all the wood logs I need. Do you need anything else?</logsansweryes>
  <logsanswerno>¿Eh? But..., oh I see, it is a joke right? Let me know when you have all the necesary wood logs. Anything else?</logsanswerno>
  <toolsanswer>Did you find my tools? Could you give them to me? I feel weird if I don't have them with me.</toolsanswer>
  <toolsansweryes>Perfect!, you are the best, we are close to leave this island together. Do you need anything else?</toolsansweryes>
  <toolsanswerno>¿Eh? But..., oh I see, it is a joke right? Let me know when you have my tools. Anything else?</toolsanswerno>
  <letsgosanswer>Everything is ready, do you want to leave the island together?</letsgosanswer>
  <letsgosansweryes>Nice! Let's go!</letsgosansweryes>
  <endgame>And then, our hero along with Eyra started a journey full of adventures...</endgame>
  <mission1>Get 10 wood logs</mission1>
  <mission2>Get back Eyra's tools</mission2>
</language>